Guide to the AIDS/Brooklyn Exhibition collection 1993.001
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Donated materials, 1945-1997
  Series 3: Donated materials, 1945-1996, includes materials donated to the Brooklyn Historical Society for the AIDS/Brooklyn exhibition. Materials include medical documentation for HIV/AIDS treatment; posters, flyers, brochures related to AIDS awareness, advocacy, and care; personal papers related to an individual's treatment, such as medication lists and notes to home health aides; materials related to an individual's childhood and career before they were diagnosed with HIV/AIDS; and photographs of people with AIDS and their families.
  Some of the people who donated materials also have an oral history in Series 1: Oral histories, 1992-1993.
  Materials primarily in English, with Haitian Coalition on AIDS materials in Haitian Creole.
  - Sub-series 3.1: Douglas Sepkowitz papers, 1987-1991
    The sub-series is in the order in which is was transferred from the Museum Division.
    Sub-series 3.1: Douglas Sepkowitz papers, 1987-1991, includes materials donated by Dr. Douglas Sepkowitz including patient and doctor-facing drug treatment information, blank treatment reports and forms, Gay Men's Health Crisis newsletters, AIDS patient assistance program and support group brochures, and HIV/AIDS educational materials. Dr. Sepkowitz was also interviewed for the oral history project.
    Gift of Dr. Douglas Sepkowitz, 1992.
    - [VIDEX AIDS Treatment Program Physician Registration Kit], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis "Treatment Issues" newsletters, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Drug Assistance Program, circa 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Patient Assistance Programs, circa 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - AIDS treatment clinical trials guides, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - HIV/AIDS educational materials, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Support groups related to HIV/AIDS, 1987-1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - HIV testing materials, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - AZT treatment reports and forms, circa 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - VIDEX ddI AIDS treatment program updates, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - VIDEX ddI blank physician/patient forms, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - VIDEX ddI individual adverse reaction reports, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - VIDEX ddI quarterly adverse effect reports, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - VIDEX ddI quarterly adverse effect reports, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - [Trimetrexate Salvage Therapy], 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - [Fluconazole treatment inquiry], 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - [Zovirax medication information], circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - [Foscavir] drug treatment information, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 3.2: Barbara Norris papers, 1988-1993
    The sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    Sub-series 3.2: Barbara Norris papers, 1988-1993, includes materials donated by Barbara Norris, such as programs and proceedings from HIV/AIDS-related benefits and conferences, HIV/AIDS awareness materials, photographs, and a certificate and news clippings from when Norris won the Nurse of Distinction award.
    Gift of Barbara Norris, 1992.
    - AIDS: The 2nd Annual Nursing Conference Proceedings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Concert for the American Foundation for AIDS Research program, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HIV/AIDS educational materials, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - AIDS awareness posters, circa 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Nurse of Distinction [award and news clippings], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - [Barbara Norris photographs], circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Event flyers related to HIV/AIDS awareness, circa 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sub-series 3.3: Alan Fleishman papers, 1985-1996
    Gift of Alan Fleishman, circa 1992.
    Most of these materials were originally donated to the Brooklyn Historical Society for the Stonewall History Project.
    This sub-series is in the order in which it was transferred from the Museum Division.
    Sub-series 3.3: Alan Fleishman papers, 1985-1996, includes news clippings and event flyers related to gay rights organizations and HIV/AIDS activism. Many of the events represented were sponsored by Gay Friends and Neighbors and Lambda Independent Democrats. There are also some programs from memorials of people who died of AIDS.
    Biographical Note
    Alan Fleishman grew up in Canarsie in Brooklyn. He was president of the Lambda Independent Democrats of Brooklyn from 1988-1990. Fleishman was a delegate to the Democratic National Convention in 1996 and 2000 and was elected District Leader to the 52nd Assembly District in 2002. Fleishman died in 2019 when he was 62 years old.
    - News clippings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Memorial programs, event flyers, 1985-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Event programs, directory of resources, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Event programs, news clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Event flyers, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Event flyers, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Gay Friends and Neighbors material, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lambda Independent Democrats material, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 3.4: James Frank Bruno papers, 1945-1992
    Sub-series 3.4: James Frank Bruno papers, 1945-1992, includes yearbooks, certificates, programs, baby books, photographs, letters, news clippings, books, a death certificate, and a will relating to James Frank Bruno's life. Most of the materials are related to Bruno's childhood, career at Citibank, and his life in New York City. Other materials, such as instructions for a home health aide, relate to Bruno and his partner Ed Marlatt's experience with HIV/AIDS.
    James Frank Bruno was born on February 23, 1945 in the Bay Ridge neighborhood of Brooklyn. Bruno attended P.S. 48 Mapleton, Edward B. Shallow Junior High School (J.H.S. 227), and New Utrecht High School. He worked for Citibank.
    Bruno met Edward (Ed) Marlatt in 1974 in Greenwich Village. They were together until Bruno's death.
    Bruno was diagnosed with AIDS in April 1989. He died in 1990.
    Gift of Ed Marlatt, 1992.
    - ["Living with AIDS: A Guide to Resources in New York City"], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - [Meditations book by Will Limón], 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - ["Chemotherapy and You" book], 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - ["Meditations for All of Us Living with AIDS" by Perry Tilleraas], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - [Edward B. Shallow Junior High School yearbooks], 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - [New Utrecht High School yearbook], 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - [Handwritten medication list], circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - [Invitation to "Dedication for Jim"], circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - [Celebration of Life program], 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - [Allan Freed Easter Jubilee program], circa 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - [Eulogies], circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - [Citibank News, community service award], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - [P.S. 48 The Mapleton School service certificate], 1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - [Baby book], 1945 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - [Passport], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - [Grave inscription], 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - [Sundance Outdoor Adventure Society card], circa 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - [Note found in desk], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - [Baby book], 1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - [List of donated items from Ed Marlatt and James Bruno], circa 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - [Home health aide instructions], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - [High school graduation invitations], 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - [Photographs and letters], 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - [HIV/AIDS in Key West articles], circa 1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - [Citibank medical benefits], circa 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - [Death certificate], 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - [Photographs and letters], circa 1950 - 1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - [The Saint, The White Party ephemera], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10, Box 10, Folder 25)
    - [Last will and testament], 1990 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series 3.5: Frank S. Hewitt papers, 1985-1991
    Sub-series 3.5: Frank S. Hewitt papers, 1985-1991, includes a list of medications Hewitt was taking in 1989, insurance claims filed from 1985-1991, and materials from his memorial service in 1990.
    The sub-series is arranged in chronological order.
    Gift of Roger Mohovich, 1992.
    Frank S. Hewitt was born on March 5, 1941 and died May 17, 1990.
    - Insurance claims, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Insurance claims, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Insurance claims, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Insurance claims, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - [List of medications], 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - [Memorial materials], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Insurance claims, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Insurance claims, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 3.6: Haitian Coalition on AIDS records, circa 1992
    Sub-series 3.6: Haitian Coalition on AIDS records, circa 1992, includes posters and brochures raising awareness about HIV/AIDS and advertising services offered by the Haitian Coalition on AIDS.
    Historical Note
    The Haitian Coalition on AIDS was founded in 1983 to support Haitian community members with HIV/AIDS, spread awareness about the disease, and advocate for people with HIV/AIDS. They had an office in downtown Brooklyn. The Haitian Coalition on AIDS was partially funded by the New York City Department of Health.
    The sub-series is in the order in which it was transferred from the Museum Division.
    - [Haitian Coalition for AIDS posters], circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - ["Lan Mó Avéti Pa Touye Kokobe" cassette tape], 1991 (Box 13, Cassette 2)
      Original Format: compact audio cassette, Duration: unknown
      Cassette tapes are not available for research use. This cassette tape is not digitized.
      This cassette tape was produced by the Haitian Coalition on AIDS in June 1991. It is Tape 4 of "Lan Mó Avéti Pa Touye Kokobe," "This cassette is made possible by a grant from the NYC Dept. of Health."
      Related Materials
      A cassette tape produced by the Haitian Coalition on AIDS in 1988 is in the Eastern Parkway Coalition records 2007.016 and is digitized and available online.
    - [Haitian Coalition on AIDS posters], circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - [Haitian Coalition on AIDS posters], circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - [Haitian Coalition on AIDS brochures], circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sub-series 3.7: Melinda Broman papers, 1986-1992
    Sub-series 3.7: Melinda Broman papers, 1986-1992, includes flyers and news clippings of HIV/AIDS-related events, letters she and her husband Victor Ockey wrote to elected officials, photographs of her and Ockey, and a program from Ockey's funeral in 1988. Also included are recorded radio and television programs about AIDS.
    - [Flyers, programs, news clippings], 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - [Letters to elected officials], 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - [Channel 13 AIDS special], 1991 (Box 13, Item 4)
      VHS. Runtime: unknown
      VHS tapes are not open for research use. This tape is not digitized.
      A VHS tape labelled "Channel 13 AIDS special, May 1, 1991."
    - [Photographs], 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - [WEBE 108 radio AIDS program], 1988 (Box 13, Cassette 1)
      This radio program (WEBE 108 Radio) begins with interviews--first with Drew, then Minna--about the loss of partners due to HIV/AIDS, and concludes with information on the most up to date medical advancements and applications, circa 1988. In their interviews, Drew and Minna discuss the death of their partners, their own physical health, family and community support they had, and their thoughts and feelings about the epidemic. The host of the program is Pamela Easton.
      Cassette tapes are not available for research use. Access to the interview is only available digitally onsite at Center for Brooklyn History's Othmer Library.
      Original Format: compact audio cassette, Duration: 01:31:25
      Drew, a gay man, was 32 years old at the time of the interview in 1988 and had been living with HIV for almost two years. He was not on medication and identified himself as asymptomatic. His partner of seven years, Donald, died on their anniversary.
      Minna, a straight, HIV-negative woman, was married to Victor, a person with hemophilia who had recently died of AIDS-related causes. (Within the AIDS/Brooklyn Oral History Project, Minna is known as Melinda Broman.)
  - Sub-series 3.8: Alan Haber papers, 1988-1993
    Gift of Estelle Haber, circa 1992.
    Alan J. Haber grew up in Brooklyn and attended Hunter College. Haber worked in communications and was spokesman for the New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission. He was diagnosed with AIDS in 1988. He left Brooklyn to live in Jerusalem, Israel in 1988 and returned in 1989. He died in 1991.
    Sub-series 3.8: Alan Haber papers, 1988-1993, includes materials related to the life of Alan J. Haber: correspondence, photographs, and an obituary. The photographs depict Haber in Israel and his name on an AIDS quilt patch sponsored by the NYC Landmarks Preservation Commission. The correspondence is photocopied letters from Haber to "Jackie." Also included is a VHS tape with "To Alan with love from Jackie" on the label.
    - [Correspondence], 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - [Obituary], 1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - [Photographs], 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ["To Alan with love from Jackie" videocassette], circa 1992 (Box 13, Item 2)
      VHS. Runtime: unknown.
      The VHS tapes are not available for research. This tape is undigitized.
      A VHS tape with "To Alan with love from Jackie" written on the label.
  - Sub-series 3.9: Gay Men's Health Crisis records, 1986-circa 1992
    Sub-series 3.9: Gay Men's Health Crisis records, 1986-circa 1992, includes a volunteer manual and flyers advertising volunteer opportunities at Gay Men's Health Crisis, as well as posters raising awareness about HIV/AIDS.
    Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) was officially established in 1982 to spread awareness about HIV/AIDS, raise money for research, and support people with AIDS. GMHC ran a hotline for information about HIV/AIDS, started a "buddy" program to help people with AIDS with day-to-day activities, and organized AIDS Walk New York. The organization is now just known as GMHC.
    - [Gay Men's Health Crisis Volunteer Manual], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis [volunteering flyers], circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - [Gay Men's Health Crisis posters], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - [Gay Men's Health Crisis posters], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Sub-series 3.10: AIDS Unity March and Rally posters, circa 1992
    Sub-series 3.10: AIDS Unity March and Rally posters, circa 1992, includes posters created for the United for AIDS Action, AIDS Unity March and Rally.
    - [United for AIDS Action, AIDS Unity March and Rally poster], circa 1992 (Folder Flat File 1)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Folder Flat File 2)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Folder Flat File 3)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Folder Flat File 4)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Folder Flat File 5)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - [Protest sign], circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Sub-series 3.11: Additional Donations, 1966-1997
    Sub-series 3.11: Additional donations, 1966-1998, includes materials donated by individuals affected by HIV/AIDS (either themselves or family members) and organizations involved in HIV/AIDS awareness and advocacy. Items include flyers, brochures, event programs, posters, obituaries, photographs, slides, and VHS tapes.
    The sub-series is arranged alphabetically.
    These materials were donated by the individual or organization indicated in the folder title unless otherwise noted. The provenance of some of these items is unknown, including the photographs and obituaries of children who died of AIDS.
    - Deborah Abraham, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Absolutely Positive, circa 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - ACT UP, circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Community Television, 1993 (Box 13, Item 1)
      VHS. Runtime: 30:00
      This VHS tape is not available for research. This material is not digitized.
      A VHS tape of "Target Bush," produced by AIDS Community Television ACT UP and AIDS activists demonstrations and protests. "This tape was originally telecast 1/19/93."
    - Body Positive, circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn AIDS Task Force, circa 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn AIDS Task Force, circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - CAMBRA [Church Avenue Merchants Block Association] AIDS Support Group, circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - [Caribbean Women's Health Association class journal], 1992 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Gift of Marilyn John, 1992.
    - [Children who died of AIDS, photograph of unknown person], circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - [Children who died of AIDS, Rebecca], 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - [Children who died of AIDS, Ronald Lou], 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - [Children who died of AIDS, Taire Kendall], 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - [Children who died of AIDS, Tomar], 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - [Philip Coleman], circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Philip Coleman, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Jerome Comer, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Casey Cronin, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Entre Hombres Project, 1991 (Box 13, Item 3)
      VHS tapes are not available for research use. This tape is undigitized.
      Video of an Entre Hombres Project social outreach event at La Escuelita, November 17, 1991. Video by Barbara Kent Productions.
    - Carney Fernandes, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Carney Fernandes, circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Michael Gallo, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Roy Gonsalves, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Jill Harris, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - [Jill Harris campaign materials], 1993 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Donna Henes, 1983-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1, Box 14, Folder 7)
    - [Donna Henes], 1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - [H. Keith Williams' HIV Primary Care Program official opening], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - H. Keith Williams' HIV Primary Care Program official opening, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - H. Keith Williams' HIV Primary Care Program official opening, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Alfred P. Ingegno, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - [Ruth Joles], circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Life Force, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lutheran Medical Center, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - [Lutheran Medical Center], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lutheran Medical Center Infection Control Department, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Mother's Love Support Network, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Gift of Mildred Pearson, 1992.
    - [Donna Mulcahy / Arthur Palmigiano], 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Donna Mulcahy, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - [A. N. Donation], circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - New York City Department of Health, Office of AIDS Surveillance, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Rhea Parham, circa 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - People with AIDS Coalition of New York, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - [Project Reach Youth], 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sandra Richardson, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - [Sandra Richardson], circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Robert Ripp, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2, Box 14)
    - Dolores Rivera, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dolores Rivera, 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dolores Rivera, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Luis Nieves [Rosa], 1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Luis Nieves [Rosa], circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - [Luis Nieves Rosa], 1992 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Willie Sandoval, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - William Sandoval, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Spellman Center for HIV-Related Disease, St. Clare's Hospital and Health Center, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - [St. Vincent's Services Positive Caring Program], 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - [St. Vincent's Hospital], circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Sam Taylor, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Alice Terson, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - [Unknown donator, flyers], 1966-1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - [Unknown donator, AIDS Forum flyer], circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - [Unknown donator, AIDS/HIV clinical trial handbook], circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - [Unknown donator, "AIDS is a Women's Issue" poster], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - [Unknown donator, "AIDS Unmasked" VHS tape], 1992 (Box 13, Item 8)
      One VHS tape labelled "AIDS Unmasked" and Sunday Morning AIDS Theatre, 8/23/1992" with the identifier FP-92-8378.
    - [Unknown donator, AIDS Walk, AIDS History Group], 1989-1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - [Unknown donator, Broken Heart pin brochure], 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - [Unknown donator, Grace Jones at Shakra's Alley flyer], circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - [Unknown donator, "Homenaje A Ramon"], circa 1992 (Box 13, Item 6)
      One VHS tape with handwritten label: "Homenaje A Ramon."
    - [Unknown donator, Note regarding Pentamidine], circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - [Unknown donator, "People with AIDS" VHS tape], circa 1990 (Box 13, Item 9)
    - [Unknown donator, photograph of unknown person], circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - [Unknown donator, unlabeled VHS tape], circa 1992 (Box 13, Item 7)
      An unlabeled VHS tape of unknown provenance.
    - [Unknown donator, "Women & AIDS," Phil Donahue Show], 1991 (Box 13, Item 5)
      A VHS tape of an episode of the Phil Donahue Show produced by Multimedia Entertainment titled "Women and AIDS," show number 072292.
    - [Unknown donator, "Women Get AIDS Too" poster], circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - [Visual AIDS], 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - [Cheryl] Wagner + [Ken] Post, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ivan Keith Weinstein, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - [Woodhull Medical and Mental Health Center, AIDS Program Services], 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - [Donge Zedo], circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)